<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Miscellaneous on An Attempt to Organise my Mind</title>
    <link>https://furrah.github.io/food/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Miscellaneous on An Attempt to Organise my Mind</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:41:47 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://furrah.github.io/food/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roasted Tomato</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/roasted-tomato/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 20:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/roasted-tomato/</guid>
      <description>A quick recipe from my house mate Lou. A great afternoon snack!
Ingredients  1 Beef tomato or tomato of your choice cut into 2-3cm chunks A few sprigs of thyme 3 Cloves of garlic - whole Olive oil Balsamic vinegar  Method  Preheat oven to 180 C Add tomato, thyme and garlic into oven tray and cover in oil Season with salt and pepper Roast for 20- 30 minutes Drizzle balsamic vinegar and remove thyme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leek and Mushroom Pie</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/leek-and-mushroom-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 22:59:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/leek-and-mushroom-pie/</guid>
      <description>Recipe taken from : Easy Peasy Foodie
Ingredients  25 g butter 2 small leeks sliced 150 g chestnut mushrooms thinly sliced 200 g Quorn chicken pieces (or 400g leftover roast chicken or 2 small chicken breasts) 1 tablespoon plain flour 1 vegetable stock cube (or 1 chicken stock cube) 300 ml boiling water 300 ml crème fraîche 1 tablespoon thyme leaves Salt and pepper 500 g block puff pastry A small amount of milk 4 large Potato&amp;rsquo;s  Method  Pre-heat the oven to 220C / 200C fan / gas mark 7 / 425F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetroot Risotto</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/beetroot-riossotto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 09:32:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/beetroot-riossotto/</guid>
      <description>Recipe taken from : BBC Good Food
Ingredients  500g fresh beetroot 2 tbsp olive oil knob of butter 1 onion, finely chopped 1 garlic clove, finely chopped 250g risotto rice 150ml white wine 700ml hot vegetable stock handful grated parmesan (or vegetarian alternative) 4 tbsp soured cream handful chopped dill  Method   Heat oven to 180C/fan 160C/gas 4. Peel and trim the beetroots (use kitchen gloves if you don’t want your hands to get stained) and cut into large wedges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Pot Mexican Quinoa</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/one-pot-mexican-quinoa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 09:15:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/one-pot-mexican-quinoa/</guid>
      <description>Recipe taken from: Damn Delicious
Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 jalapeno, minced 1 cup quinoa 1 cup vegetable broth 1 (15-ounce) can black beans, drained and rinsed 1 (14.5 oz) can fire-roasted diced tomatoes 1 cup corn kernels, frozen, canned or roasted 1 teaspoon chili powder 1/2 teaspoon cumin Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper, to taste 1 avocado, halved, seeded, peeled and diced Juice of 1 lime 2 tablespoons chopped fresh cilantro leaves  Method  Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flapjack</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/flapjack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 14:09:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/flapjack/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  250g porridge oats 125g butter 125g brown sugar 3 tbsp golden syrup 50g walnuts 25g almonds  Method  Preheat oven to 180°C On a low heat add buter, sugar, and golden syrup to a pan. Heat until sugar has lost granularity Add porridge oats, walnuts, almonds, whatever else you want to add. Line a 20x20cm baking tray and pour oat mixture in. Place in oven for 20 mins or until golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>