<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Miscellaneous on An Attempt to Organise my Mind</title>
    <link>https://furrah.github.io/food/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Miscellaneous on An Attempt to Organise my Mind</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:41:47 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://furrah.github.io/food/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Sweet Potatoes</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/baked-sweet-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 23:14:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/baked-sweet-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  4 medium (~1/3 lb each) sweet potatoes 1 15-ounce can chickpeas (rinsed and drained) 1/2 Tbsp olive oil 1/2 tsp each cumin, coriander, cinnamon, smoked (or regular) paprika 1 pinch sea salt or lemon juice (optional)  Garlic Herb Sauce  1/4 cup hummus (or tahini) 1/2 medium lemon, juiced (1/2 lemon yields ~1 Tbsp juice) 3 cloves garlic, minced (3 cloves yield ~1 1/2 Tbsp or 9 g) Water or unsweetened almond milk (to thin) Sea salt to taste (optional)  Toppings  1/4 cup cherry tomatoes (diced) 1/4 cup chopped parsley (minced) 2 Tbsp lemon juice Chili garlic sauce  Instructions  Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (204 C) and line a large baking sheet with foil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetroot Risotto</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/beetroot-riossotto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 09:32:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/beetroot-riossotto/</guid>
      <description>Recipe taken from : BBC Good Food
Ingredients  500g fresh beetroot 2 tbsp olive oil knob of butter 1 onion, finely chopped 1 garlic clove, finely chopped 250g risotto rice 150ml white wine 700ml hot vegetable stock handful grated parmesan (or vegetarian alternative) 4 tbsp soured cream handful chopped dill  Method   Heat oven to 180C/fan 160C/gas 4. Peel and trim the beetroots (use kitchen gloves if you don’t want your hands to get stained) and cut into large wedges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Pot Mexican Quinoa</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/one-pot-mexican-quinoa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 09:15:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/one-pot-mexican-quinoa/</guid>
      <description>Recipe taken from: Damn Delicious
Ingredients  1 tablespoon olive oil 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 jalapeno, minced 1 cup quinoa 1 cup vegetable broth 1 (15-ounce) can black beans, drained and rinsed 1 (14.5 oz) can fire-roasted diced tomatoes 1 cup corn kernels, frozen, canned or roasted 1 teaspoon chili powder 1/2 teaspoon cumin Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper, to taste 1 avocado, halved, seeded, peeled and diced Juice of 1 lime 2 tablespoons chopped fresh cilantro leaves  Method  Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flapjack</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/flapjack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 14:09:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/flapjack/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  250g porridge oats 125g butter 125g brown sugar 3 tbsp golden syrup 50g walnuts 25g almonds  Method  Preheat oven to 180°C On a low heat add buter, sugar, and golden syrup to a pan. Heat until sugar has lost granularity Add porridge oats, walnuts, almonds, whatever else you want to add. Line a 20x20cm baking tray and pour oat mixture in. Place in oven for 20 mins or until golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>