<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eukarya on Well lets take a look at it, Mr Gumby!</title>
    <link>https://furrah.github.io/eukarya/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eukarya on Well lets take a look at it, Mr Gumby!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:29:45 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://furrah.github.io/eukarya/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fungi</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/eukarya/fungi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:29:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/eukarya/fungi/</guid>
      <description>Introduction An attempt at identifying fungi. There&amp;rsquo;s a strong chance I am 99% wrong.
Stinkhorn - Close to Greenham Common Nature Reserve - Berkshire Out walking with my friend Will searching for one of the last blooming orchids in the UK - Autumn Lady Tresses. We didn&amp;rsquo;t find any unfortunately but we did find these!     Chicken of the woods - Bagley Wood - Oxfordshire Apparently as the name suggests it tastes of chicken&amp;hellip; or at least is a good replacement for chicken!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing Avocados</title>
      <link>https://furrah.github.io/eukarya/growing_avocado/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 17:51:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://furrah.github.io/eukarya/growing_avocado/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve just got back from the Isle of Skye in Scotland and have bought back 20 Avocado seeds left over from a weeks worth of communal meals. I&amp;rsquo;ve just moved to Oxford, although I am currently staying with my friend Adam in Abingdon and have decided to propagate the seeds in his apartment. Thanks Adam.
14th September 2021 Tooth pick up the seeds and suspend in water. There is a better method for this which is suspending the seed from the top and not tripoding like I have done.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
